[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What kind of response to the worst school shooting in American history is that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, as you know, this is something the president as you know, feels really personally deeply about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States Senate"], "PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ":", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Isn't that what the president should now be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, I think that is what the president has been saying to both members -- to both parties, and you know, the reality in the senate today is that the overwhelming majority of Democrats support background checks, and all we need is a small minority of Republicans in the United States Senate to join with the 90 percent of Americans to support doing this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "How would you sum up her tenure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I think I come from the opposite side of the political divide, if you like, being a labor prime minister.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Why was she so divisive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Look, she took some very difficult decisions and she took decisions that were often extremely unpopular, so you know, even though over here in America, she would be I think admired probably both sides of the divide.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "What was she like in private, Margaret Thatcher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, the fascinating thing because obviously, I grew up in the sense politically with her as the prime minister, very distant figure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Are you speaking as somebody who perhaps is in a similar position, a divisive reaction perhaps back home, but oddly popular perhaps in America as she indeed has proven to be today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Look, I think part of the problem is in modern politics particularly, that if you're in power for any length of time, you take difficult decisions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Rudy, she was quite something, wasn't she, Margaret Thatcher?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "She sure was.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Why is that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "First of all, including by me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Can you recognize that in somebody like her who was so consumed by the job and the power?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Great Britain"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What do you think her legacy should be, Rudy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "UILIANI: Well, I think revitalizing Great Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rudy?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "This is going to be a big failure, isn't it, for President Obama if he can't do better than this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "First of all, we don't know what's going to happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cuomo"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "RB", ":", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "I mean, should he be doing more of the Cuomo style of campaigning on this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, I think what Cuomo did was he put together a very -- even a stricter gun control approach.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cuomo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "So you would encourage Republicans not to filibuster?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "I would not only encourage it, I don't understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "How you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Very well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Churchill"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "RB", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Niall Ferguson, as a fellow Brit, where does Margaret Thatcher rank in the pantheon of British prime ministers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Second only to Churchill, I would say.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Niall Ferguson", "Margaret Thatcher"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Niall"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "But where does she stand globally, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Oh, I would agree with Niall.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Would we be looking at Margaret Thatcher in a different way if she had been a man presiding over that period in Great Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "For the most part, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"], "LOCATION": ["Great Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Margaret Thatcher"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Was it fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well, I have been enjoying your show not least because I heard a former editor of \"The Daily Mirror\" and a former Labor prime minister say positive things about Margaret Thatcher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "can I disagree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "Yeah, you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Japan"]}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Is he doing the right kind of things with North Korea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, I think we need to do more to help Japan right now and have a new American military strategy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130408pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "EX", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Niall Ferguson, guns and America, is there ever going to be a significant cultural change in America in relation to guns, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, I really wish there would be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Niall Ferguson"], "LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}]